# Prisha Thakkar

### PSYCHOLOGY GRADUATE | KATHAK DANCER & TEACHER

I am a student of psychology finished my third year of Bachelors in Arts. I consider myself to be an upbeat leader, success driven, self-motivated, goal-oriented and a passionate multitasker. I have been learning the Indian classical dance form kathak for the past 12 years and am teaching for the past 4 years.

### AKHIL BHARATIYA GANDHARVA MAHAVIDYALAYA.

2022. Visharad Purna in Kathak

## **Expert Skills**

imovies

-	
Human Resource Management • • • • •	
Employee Engagement &	
Welfare	
Performance Management	••••
Onboarding	• • • • •
Recruitment	• • • • •
Basic Computer Skills	• • • •
SPSS	• • • •
Problem Solving	• • • • •
Observation Skills	• • • • •
Leadership	• • • • •
Communication	• • • • •
Empathy	• • • • •
Active Listening	• • • • •
Research	• • • • •
СВТ	• • • • •
Counselling	• • • • •
diting apps like filmora	&

# **Education History**

#### UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA

2022. Human Resource Management: HR for people managers
Preparing to Manage Human Resources,
Managing Employee Compensation,
Human Resources Management
Capstone: HR for People Managers,
Recruiting, Hiring, and Onboarding
Employees & Managing Employee
Performance

#### FERGUSSON COLLEGE, PUNE

2019-2022. Bachelors in Arts (Psychology) *CGPA*: 9.96/10

#### ARMY PUBLIC SCHOOL,

#### **KIRKEE**

2017-2019. Higher Secondary Education - 11th and 12th Percentage: 91.8% :PCB Psychology BISHOP'S CO-ED SCHOOL,

#### KALYANI NAGAR

2017. Secondary Education - 10th Percentage: 95.33% : Science

## **Work Experience**

#### KATHAK TEACHER & PERFORMER

#### Rujuta Soman Cultural Academy | Jun 2019current

- Head of the kalyani nagar branch of RSCA
- Training students of beginner and intermediate level
- handling accounts and finances
- performed at various platforms

#### **EVENT MANAGEMENT**

#### Cultural events | 2020-2022

- Content writing and digital marketing for RSCA
- Core team member

#### **VOLUNTEER**

#### PsyFy College Club | 2019-2020

- Volunteer at college fest
- Event Management

## **Hobbies**

Fitness & Yoga

Music Instruments

Dance

Music

Travel & Adventure

## Research & Testing

- Developed a forty item questionnaire on Emotional Literacy with a reliability coefficient of 0.86 (October'20 –January'21)
- Conducted research on the effect of sibling relationships, attachment and adjustment in later life (Feb' 21-June'21)
- Working on a research study on Impact of being a dancer on Emotional Literacy, Time perspective, Self esteem and psychological well-being(Ongoing)

### **Contact**



prisha.thakkar1809@gmail.com



+91 9595520202



Pune, Maharashtra, India.

## **Courses & Trainings**

#### PSYCH SCHOOL, INDIA

Internship -Counselling Skills Training Program | 2021 - 2022.

- Training in Counselling Skills, Client-Counsellor RelationshipManagement in different Circumstances
- Ways to Manage one's Mental Health as a Mental Health Professional.
- Role plays by becoming client and psychologist

# PSYLENS CENTRE - CBT FOR SOCIAL ANXIETY

**Dec 21'**.Learned the types of treatment plans that can be used to treat patients with social anxiety and how to implement them.

#### **COURSERA**

- 2020. The University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill.
   Positive Psychology
- 2020. Johns Hopkins University.
  Psychological First Aid
- 2020. The University of Edinburgh. Know Thyself - The Unconscious

#### **UDEMY - 2020**

- Become a Pro handwriting analyst
- Handwriting Analysis A to Z
- Signature Analysis: Beginner to Advance
- 21 Day Happiness Challenge
- Life Coach Yourself
- Relationship Coaching- best tools for relationship
- The Complete Digital Marketing Course
- Internationally Accredited Diploma in Yoga Training